http://www.law.yale.edu/about-yale-law-school/offices-services/information-technology-services-its-yale-law-school/yale-law-school-website-privacy-policy

Yale Law School Website Privacy Policy - Yale Law School
<![endif]-->
Skip Navigation
Studying Law at YaleOur FacultyCenters & WorkshopsStudent Life
Admissions & Financial Aid
JD AdmissionsGraduate AdmissionsFinancial AidNondiscrimination, Title IX, and Clery Act Statements
YLS Today
YLS Today
NewsEventsIn The PressVideosReports & PublicationsSocial MediaMedia InquiriesSubmit an Event
Centers & Workshops
Paul Tsai China CenterCollaboration for Research Integrity and Transparency (CRIT)Cultural Cognition ProjectGlobal Health Justice PartnershipGruber Program for Global Justice and Women’s RightsHuman Rights Workshop: Current Issues & EventsInformation Society ProjectJohn M. Olin Center for Law, Economics and Public Policy
The Justice CollaboratoryAbdallah S. Kamel Center for the Study of Islamic Law and CivilizationLaw, Economics & Organization WorkshopLaw, Ethics & Animals ProgramLaw School Access ProgramLegal History ForumLegal Theory WorkshopThe Arthur Liman Center for Public Interest Law
Middle East Legal Studies SeminarThe Oscar M. Ruebhausen FundOrville H. Schell, Jr. Center for International Human RightsRobina Foundation Human Rights Fellowship InitiativeThe Solomon Center for Health Law and PolicyYale Center for Law and PhilosophyYale Center for Environmental Law and Policy
Yale Law School Center for Global Legal ChallengesYale Law School Center for the Study of Corporate LawYale Law School Center for Private LawYale Law School Latin American Legal StudiesQuinnipiac-Yale Dispute Resolution WorkshopBert Wasserman Workshop in Law and FinanceWorkshop on Chinese Legal Reform
Student Life
Our School & LocationStudent ServicesCareer DevelopmentHealth & Wellness
Welcome Class of 2023Student News & OpinionPrograms and Opportunities
Student Journals & OrganizationsDiscrimination and HarassmentCommencement
Diversity & InclusionTitle IXPolicies, Resources, and Reporting
Search
Search
Studying Law at Yale
back
Studying Law at Yale
Areas of InterestDegree ProgramsClinical and Experiential LearningCoursesAcademic Calendar & ResourcesAlumni & Student ProfilesLaw Library
Our Faculty
back
Our Faculty
FacultyLecturers & AffiliatesFaculty Activities & Scholarship
Centers & Workshops
back
Centers & Workshops
Paul Tsai China CenterCollaboration for Research Integrity and Transparency (CRIT)Cultural Cognition ProjectGlobal Health Justice PartnershipGruber Program for Global Justice and Women’s RightsHuman Rights Workshop: Current Issues & EventsInformation Society ProjectJohn M. Olin Center for Law, Economics and Public PolicyThe Justice CollaboratoryAbdallah S. Kamel Center for the Study of Islamic Law and CivilizationLaw, Economics & Organization WorkshopLaw, Ethics & Animals ProgramLaw School Access ProgramLegal History ForumLegal Theory WorkshopThe Arthur Liman Center for Public Interest LawMiddle East Legal Studies SeminarThe Oscar M. Ruebhausen FundOrville H. Schell, Jr. Center for International Human RightsRobina Foundation Human Rights Fellowship InitiativeThe Solomon Center for Health Law and PolicyYale Center for Law and PhilosophyYale Center for Environmental Law and PolicyYale Law School Center for Global Legal ChallengesYale Law School Center for the Study of Corporate LawYale Law School Center for Private LawYale Law School Latin American Legal StudiesQuinnipiac-Yale Dispute Resolution WorkshopBert Wasserman Workshop in Law and FinanceWorkshop on Chinese Legal Reform
Student Life
back
Student Life
Our School & LocationStudent ServicesCareer DevelopmentHealth & WellnessWelcome Class of 2023Student News & OpinionPrograms and OpportunitiesStudent Journals & OrganizationsDiscrimination and HarassmentCommencementDiversity & InclusionTitle IXPolicies, Resources, and Reporting
Admissions & Financial Aid
back
Admissions & Financial Aid
JD AdmissionsGraduate AdmissionsFinancial AidNondiscrimination, Title IX, and Clery Act Statements
YLS Today
back
YLS Today
NewsEventsIn The PressVideosReports & PublicationsSocial MediaMedia InquiriesSubmit an Event
Alumni
Faculty
Staff
Students
COVID-19
Yale Law School Website Privacy Policy
HomeAbout Yale Law SchoolOffices & ServicesInformation Technology Services (ITS)Yale Law School Website Privacy Policy
Yale Law School is committed to protecting your privacy. Any information you voluntarily provide to us through a Yale Law School website such as email address, name, or phone number will never be sold or traded to other colleges, universities, nonprofit organizations, or businesses. Yale Law School might use this information to inform you of changes to that website or to provide you other news and information about that site that we believe would be of interest to you.   Information gathered automaticallyUnless you take steps to browse the Internet anonymously, or opt-out, Yale Law School, similar to most institutions and organizations on the Internet, tracks web browsing patterns to inform understanding of how our sites are being used. Generic information is collected through the use of "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to evaluate usage patterns so that we can improve both content and distribution. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, doing so may prevent you from using the full functionality of all of our websites. The generic information we collect is based on IP address, which is the location of a computer or network, and is not linked to your specific email address in any of the reports or other material compiled by Yale Law School. Yale Law School will not associate your IP address and web usage data with any other information held by Yale Law School that can specifically identify you unless required to do so by law.
Some sections of Yale Law School websites use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use our sites. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website includes your IP address. This information will be transmitted to and stored by Google on its servers. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Please visit the following pages for more information on Google Analytics terms of use and Google's privacy practices.
Information you provide to usTo communicate effectively with visitors to our website, we may ask you for personally identifiable information that can include, by way of illustration, name, email address or phone number. Yale Law School will never sell or trade personally identifiable information you voluntarily provide to us such as name, email address or phone number, to other colleges, universities, nonprofit organizations, or businesses unless one or more of the following conditions apply:
We have your consent to share the information.
We are sharing such information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes
External linksSome parts of the Yale Law School website may contain links to external websites not owned by, or officially affiliated with, Yale Law School in any way. Yale Law School is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Contact information
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this website, you can contact:
Yale Law School Office of Public Affairspublicaffairs.law@yale.edu
Consumer Information (ABA Required Disclosures)
This website is supported by the Oscar M. Ruebhausen Fund at Yale Law School
